http://www.wsib.on.ca/en/privacy

Skip to main content
Personal Information and privacy policy
Protecting your privacy at the Workplace Safety & Insurance Board
The WSIB is committed to protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. Your personal information is protected under the Workplace Safety & Insurance Act and the Freedom of Information & Protection of Privacy Act.
Privacy statement for workers
The Privacy Statement explains what information the WSIB collects about you and how it is used, retained and disclosed by the organization.
Our Privacy Statement for Workers is available in multiple languages:
Arabic (PDF)
Simplified Chinese (PDF)
Traditional Chinese (PDF)
Croatian (PDF)
Italian (PDF)
Polish (PDF)
Portuguese (PDF)
Punjabi (PDF)
Russian (PDF)
Serbian (PDF)
Spanish (PDF)
Tamil (PDF)
Vietnamese (PDF)
Privacy FAQs
For more information about privacy and how we are committed to protecting your confidential information, read our Privacy FAQs:
FAQs for Workers
FAQs for Employers
FAQs for Health Care Practitioners
FAQs for the General Public
Corporate access and privacy statement
The WSIB's Corporate Access and Privacy Statement documents our corporate and information management practices. Release of this statement supports the principles of openness and transparency in how we do business, and reflects commitment to responsible stewardship.
Operational Policy Manual
Policies on Access to Claim File Information and Confidentiality
Do you need to register with us?
Your Guide: Services and Responsibilities – Business Edition
Your Guide: Benefits, Services and Responsibilities – Worker Edition
